Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:
aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：
是的，是的，船长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
船长：♪ 然后降落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
SpongeBob: 97, 98, 99...
海绵宝宝：97、98、99……
100.
Ok, Gary, let's do
the other side now.
好的，加里，我们开始吧
现在另一边。
Gary?
加里？
Can you hear that?
你能听到吗？
Oh, Squidward, it's you.
哦，章鱼哥，是你。
I thought I heard something.
我以为我听到了什么。
SpongeBob, I've been sitting
here motionless for 45 minutes.
海绵宝宝，我一直坐着
在这里一动不动45分钟。
What could you possibly
have heard me doing?
你可能会做什么
有听到我在做什么吗？
Breathing.
呼吸。
SpongeBob, I will give you $5
if you let me enjoy the rest
of my morning in peace.
海绵宝宝，我给你5美元
如果你让我享受剩下的时光
我平静的早晨。
Ok.
好的。
Hey, I could've sworn
I had $5 in here.
嘿，我可以发誓
我这里有 5 美元。
I have it, Squidward.
我有它，章鱼哥。
You gave it to me
to leave you alone yesterday.
你给了我
昨天让你一个人呆着。
Squidward, you can have
the $5 back.
章鱼哥，你可以拥有
5 美元返还。
Mr. Krabs says...
蟹老板说……
I don't care
what Mr. Krabs says.
我不在乎
蟹老板说的话。
I just want...
我只想...
Coffee rain!
咖啡雨！
It's hot chocolate.
这是热巧克力。
Chocolate rain!
巧克力雨！
Squidward.
章鱼哥。
Squidward, wait!
章鱼哥，等等！
It's locked.
它被锁了。
SpongeBob: Squidward.
海绵宝宝：章鱼哥。
Squid...ward.
鱿鱼……病房。
Huh?
啊？
The key.
关键。
Oh, where did I put
that stupid...
哦，我放哪儿了
那个傻...
Squidward.
章鱼哥。
Oh, why can't I just find the...
哦，为什么我找不到...
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
What?
什么？
You left your keys on
the table back there.
你把钥匙开着
后面的桌子。
Hey, Squidward.
嘿，章鱼哥。
Yes?
是的？
Didn't you used to have one
of those cucumber bicycles?
你以前不是有一个吗
那些黄瓜自行车？
Oh,  .
哦，  。
That was a recumbent bicycle,
and I sold it.
那是一辆卧式自行车，
我把它卖了。
Why?
为什么？
So I could get further
away from you!
所以我可以走得更远
离你远点！
Ok, I'll see you
later then, Squidward.
好的，我会见到你
后来，章鱼哥。
Bon voyage, nincompoop.
一路顺风，傻瓜。
What the?
什么？
Can I help you, Officer?
我可以帮你吗，警官？
No.
不。
But you can help yourself
to this ticket.
但你可以帮助自己
到这张票。
Ticket?
票？
Officer, please.
军官，请。
I have impeccable boat smarts.
我拥有无可挑剔的驾船智慧。
I pride myself in maintaining
an unsoiled driving record.
我为自己能够保持
未受污染的驾驶记录
It's all that I have.
这就是我所拥有的一切。
Well, you can have it again
right after you complete
boating school.
嗯，你可以再拥有一次
right after you complete
boating school.
Boating school.
划船学校。
Oh, well.
那好吧。
It's just one day out
of your life, Squiddy.
这只是一天的时间
你的生活，鱿鱼。
How bad could it be?
有多糟糕？
Oh, Squidward.
哦，章鱼哥。
Good morning, class.
早上好，同学们。
Would everyone please
take a seat?
请大家
请坐吗？
Psst, Squidward.
嘘，章鱼哥。
Sit here.
坐在这里。
Here.
这里。
Um, excuse me.
嗯，对不起。
There don't seem to be
any empty seats left.
好像没有
剩余的空座位。
But there's one
right next to SpongeBob.
但有一个
就在海绵宝宝旁边。
Do you mind?
你介意吗？
Don't worry, Squidward.
别担心，章鱼哥。
We're boating buddies now.
我们现在是划船的伙伴了。
I'll teach you everything
I know, and then we can...
我会教你一切
我知道，然后我们可以...
We won't be doing anything,
because there is no "we".
我们不会做任何事
因为没有“我们”。
Understand?
理解？
Quiet in the front, please.
请前面安静。
Oh, I understand.
哦，我明白了。
I understand perfectly...
boating buddy.
我完全理解...
划船的朋友。
Mrs. Puff: Ok, class.
普芙老师：好的，同学们。
Why don't we get
to know our new students
为什么我们不得到
了解我们的新学生
by telling each other why
we were sentenced to...
通过告诉对方原因
我们被判...
I mean, why we are enrolled
in boating school.
我的意思是，我们为什么注册
在划船学校。
Um, I got caught speeding.
嗯，我超速被抓了。
Very good.
非常好。
Next.
下一个。
I don't see what's
so very good about it.
我不明白是什么
非常好。
No, I didn't mean very...
不，我的意思不是很...
I know what you meant.
我知道你的意思。
Next.
下一个。
I am here because my...
我来这里是因为我的...
We all know why
you're here, SpongeBob.
我们都知道为什么
你在这里，海绵宝宝。
What about you, sir?
先生，你呢？
What, me?
什么，我？
Yes.
是的。
Would you like to tell
the rest of the class
why you're with us today?
你想告诉吗
班里的其他人
你今天为什么和我们在一起？
Why, I...
为什么，我...
All right, I'll tell you.
好吧，我告诉你。
I was trying
to get away from him!
我正在尝试
远离他！
He is the bane of my existence.
他是我存在的祸根。
Yours too?
你的也是吗？
Uh, what I meant to say was,
please come up to the chalkboard
呃，我想说的是，
请到黑板前来
and draw a diagram
of the incident.
并画出图表
事件的经过。
Squidward: Gladly.
章鱼哥：很高兴。
It all started
when I left my house.
一切都开始了
当我离开家时。
And then he appeared.
然后他出现了。
He made an immediate
right turn and parked...
他立即做出了
右转并停车...
...here.
...这里。
Seeing the oncoming hazard,
I looked both ways and proceeded
safely toward my vehicle.
看到即将来临的危险，
我向两边看了看然后继续
安全地驶向我的车辆。
It was then that I realized
I was being followed
at an unsafe distance.
那时我才意识到
我被跟踪了
在不安全的距离。
So in order to create
more optimal driving conditions
所以为了创建
更优化的驾驶条件
I was forced to then partake
in evasive action.
然后我被迫参加
在回避动作中。
And by increasing speed slightly
并稍微提高速度
I created a safety cushion
while inadvertently attracting
我创造了一个安全垫
在不经意间吸引
the attention of said
law enforcement official.
所说的注意
执法官员。
May I sit down now,
sweet cheeks?
我现在可以坐下吗
甜蜜的脸颊？
Why, certainly.
为什么，当然。
And perhaps now
也许现在
SpongeBob would like
to come up and illustrate
his side of the story.
海绵宝宝想要
上来并说明
他的故事。
His side?
他这边？
Well, first, I started
over here, and then,
I went way over here.
嗯，首先，我开始了
在这里，然后，
我走到这里了。
Doo-doo-doo-doo-doo, like that.
嘟嘟嘟嘟嘟，就这样。
And then,
I went around like this,
and over here like that
然后，
我就这样绕了一圈
就在这里
and across this way,
and then down here
穿过这条路，
然后到这里
and over here like this,
and then...
在这里像这样
然后...
And then, I came around
and stopped right here.
然后我就过来了
就停在这里。
Class: SpongeBob and Squidward,
best boating buddies forever?
班级：海绵宝宝和章鱼哥，
永远最好的划船伙伴？
Do you like it, Squidward?
你喜欢吗，章鱼哥？
Shut it.
闭嘴。
Ah, lunch time,
eh, boating buddy?
啊，午餐时间，
呃，划船的朋友吗？
I'll have to eat over here,
just like back in grade school.
我一定要来这里吃饭
就像回到小学一样。
Squidward, you got any
extra mustard in there?
章鱼哥，你有什么
那里有额外的芥末吗？
Mm, bon appetit, Squiddy.
嗯，胃口好，鱿鱼。
you've ruined my morning,
you've ruined my lunch,
and you're ruining my...
你毁了我的早晨
你毁了我的午餐
而你正在毁掉我的...
Mrs. Puff: Ok, class.
普芙老师：好的，同学们。
It's time for our behind
the wheel lesson.
是时候我们的背后了
轮子课。
Squidward, you'll be riding
with SpongeBob.
章鱼哥，你会骑马
与海绵宝宝。
Yeah, I never saw that coming.
是的，我从来没有预见到会发生这种事。
Now, we're gonna take
this nice and slow.
现在，我们要采取
这又好又慢。
SpongeBob, what do we do
when pulling away from the curb?
海绵宝宝，我们该怎么办
当驶离路边时？
Step on the gas?
踩油门吗？
Good.
好的。
Nice and easy.
又好又容易。
Now let's slow...
现在让我们慢慢...
SpongeBob, look out!
海绵宝宝，小心！
SpongeBob, give me the wheel.
海绵宝宝，把方向盘给我。
I got it, I got it.
我明白了，我明白了。
Just let go of it!
放开它吧！
Hooligans!
流氓！
Johnson, I've finally
figured out a way
约翰逊，我终于
想出了一个办法
to shrink an ordinary mailman
down to the size
of a grain of sand.
缩小一个普通的邮递员
缩小到尺寸
一粒沙子。
But how?
但如何呢？
By using this shrink ray.
通过使用这种收缩射线。
Mother of mercy!
慈母慈悲！
Where'd they go?
他们去哪儿了？
Scientist: There.
科学家：在那里。
They're headed right for
that discarded potato chip.
他们正前往
那个被丢弃的薯片
What's the matter?
怎么了？
Potato chips
are his favorite snack.
薯片
是他最喜欢的零食。
Johnson!
约翰逊！
No!
不！
No, no, no.
不，不，不。
I never will understand
these city folk.
我永远不会明白
这些城里人。
SpongeBob: Hey,
where'd Squidward go?
海绵宝宝：嘿，
章鱼哥去哪儿了？
I was just leaving.
我正要离开。
Mrs. Puff: Ok, class, it's time
to take our final exam.
Mrs. Puff：好的，同学们，时间到了
参加我们的期末考试。
Please have your pencils ready.
请准备好你的铅笔。
Psst.
嘘。
Hey, boating buddy.
嘿，划船的朋友。
If you need any help, I've taken
this test hundreds of times.
如果您需要任何帮助，我已经采取了
这样的测试已经有数百次了。
How many times
do I have to tell you?
多少次
我必须告诉你吗？
I am not your buddy.
我不是你的朋友。
I don't need your help,
and I don't need you, ever!
我不需要你的帮助
我永远不需要你！
Now, just kindly let me
take this stupid test
现在，请让我
参加这个愚蠢的测试
so I can get out of here
and never have to see you again
for the rest of my life.
这样我就可以离开这里
永远不必再见到你
我的余生。
Ok, Squidward, if that's
the way you want it.
好吧，章鱼哥，如果是的话
你想要的方式。
Thank you.
谢谢。
three more minutes, class.
还有三分钟，上课。
SpongeBob.
海绵宝宝。
SpongeBob, I need your help.
海绵宝宝，我需要你的帮助。
Mrs. Puff: Two more minutes.
普夫夫人：还有两分钟。
SpongeBob, please?
海绵宝宝，请吗？
This is important.
这很重要。
You said you didn't
need my help, Squidward,
and that you didn't need me.
你说你没有
需要我的帮助，章鱼哥，
并且你不需要我。
No, no, I didn't.
不，不，我没有。
I never said that.
我从来没有这么说过。
I don't need your help,
and I don't need you.
我不需要你的帮助
我不需要你。
Jerk.
混蛋。
All right, I said it,
but that was before.
好吧，我说了，
但那是以前的事了。
Before what?
在什么之前？
Before... Before...
之前……之前……
Mrs. Puff: One more
minute, class.
泡芙夫人：再来一张
分钟，上课。
Before we were...
, boating buddies.
之前我们...
，划船的朋友。
Yay!
耶！
Mrs. Puff: Okay, class,
time is up.
泡芙老师：好的，同学们，
时间到了。
Time can't be up.
时间不能到了。
I didn't get a chance
to fill in a single answer.
我没有机会
填写一个答案。
What am I supposed to do?
我该怎么办？
You do the same thing
that everybody else does
who fails the test.
你做同样的事情
其他人都这样做
谁没有通过测试。
You take it again next week.
你下周再服用一次。
Next week?
下周？
Don't worry, Squidward.
别担心，章鱼哥。
I've never gotten one answer
right on this test
我一直没有得到一个答案
就在这次测试中
but we'll meet again next week
at Mrs. Puff's boating school.
但我们下周会再见面
在普夫夫人的划船学校。
SpongeBob: Order up!
海绵宝宝：快下单吧！
How's it lookin' out there, boy?
孩子，外面看起来怎么样？
Like two more
satisfied regulars, Mr. K.
还喜欢两个
满意的常客，K 先生。
I ain't interested in the same
old regulars, SpongeBob.
我对同样的事情不感兴趣
老常客，海绵宝宝。
So I took out an ad
in the Bikini Bottom Examiner
to bring in some new customers.
于是我就拿出了一个广告
在比基尼底部检查器中
引进一些新客户。
'Twas a bargain too.
这也很划算。
Only cost me a nickel.
只花了我五分钱。
So tell me now, boy.
所以现在告诉我，孩子。
How many new customers
we got out there so far?
有多少新客户
到目前为止我们已经到了那里了吗？
Ooh, uh, let me see.
哦，呃，让我看看。
There was... none.
没有……没有。
What?
什么？
What do you mean, none?
什么意思，没有？
Don't these people
read the paper?
难道这些人
读报纸？
Ooh.
哦。
This thing hasn't been
touched in months.
这件事还没有
几个月来触动。
While that paper is sellin'
like Krabby Patties.
当那张纸正在卖的时候
像蟹黄饼一样。
Eh, pardon me, sir.
呃，请原谅我，先生。
Could I interest you in a copy
of the Examiner this fine day?
我可以给你一份副本吗
考官在这个美好的日子？
Nobody reads the Examiner, bud.
没有人读《审查员》，伙计。
It's all full of
boring charts and facts.
都充满了
无聊的图表和事实。
The Bottom Feeder
is where it's at.
底部进料器
就是它所在的地方。
It's got, like,
interesting stories and stuff.
它有，比如，
有趣的故事和东西。
Fish boy strikes again?
鱼男孩又来袭？
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Aren't these stories
a little less than truthful?
这些故事不就是
有点不诚实？
I don't know,
but they're selling.
我不知道，
但他们正在卖。
Yes, they certainly are.
是的，他们当然是。
Please, allow me.
请允许我。
Thank you.
谢谢。
No, thank you.
不，谢谢。
Now, let's see how much
they charge for advertising.
现在让我们看看有多少
他们收取广告费。
25 cents per word?
每个字25美分？
The newspaper business
sure is easy money.
报纸业务
当然是很容易赚钱。
That gives me an idea.
这给了我一个想法。
What a "fantabulastical" day,
Eh, Squiddy?
多么“梦幻”的一天啊
呃，鱿鱼？
Yep, another wonderful,
humdrum day slinging burgers.
是的，另一个精彩，
乏味的一天吊着汉堡。
Off of your duff, boy.
别再胡闹了，孩子。
You think I spent all last night
assembling this printing press
你以为我昨晚度过了整个晚上
组装这台印刷机
so you could
laze around all day?
所以你可以
整天闲逛？
From now on,
you'll be twice as busy, and
I expect you to wear two hats
从现在开始，
你会加倍忙碌，并且
我希望你戴两顶帽子
'cause along with
your usual fry-cookin' duties
因为随着
你平常的煎炸工作
you're my lead reporter
for the new Krabby Kronicle.
你是我的首席记者
新款 Krabby Kronicle。
Oh, my very own press badge!
哦，我自己的记者徽章！
That's right, boy.
没错，孩子。
And here's your very own camera.
这是您自己的相机。
See, you'll need it to document
all them juicy stories
you're gonna write.
看，你需要它来记录
所有这些有趣的故事
你会写。
Well, what are you
waitin' for, boy?
好吧，你是什么？
还在等吗，小伙子？
The public thirsts for
a juicy story, Eh?
公众渴望
一个有趣的故事，嗯？
Hm, but what kind of story
is juicy enough to quench
their dry news gullets?
嗯，但是什么样的故事
多汁足以解渴
他们的枯燥新闻咽喉？
I don't even know where
to begin to look.
我什至不知道在哪里
开始寻找。
hm, no news to report here.
嗯，这里没有消息可报道。
Stop the presses, it's Patrick!
停止媒体报道，是帕特里克！
And he appears to be
waiting for the bus.
而他似乎是
等公共汽车。
This is the kind
of breaking story my readers
are waiting for.
就是这样的
我的读者的突发新闻
正在等待。
Patrick Star?
帕特里克·斯塔？
I'm Scoup SquarePants
from the Krabby Kronicle.
我是勺子方裤
来自克拉比纪事报。
Everyone's wondering,
what bus are you taking today?
大家都在好奇，
你今天乘什么公共汽车？
Oh, I'm not taking
a bus, SpongeBob.
哦，我不带
公共汽车，海绵宝宝。
I am watching this pole,
so the next time it moves,
I will see it.
我看着这根柱子，
所以下次它移动的时候
我会看到的。
Whoa, this story is juicy.
哇，这个故事很有趣。
What a "money-tastical" day,
Eh, Mr. Squidward?
真是一个“金钱狂”的日子啊
呃，章鱼哥先生？
Yeah, I'm just raking it in.
是的，我只是把它收起来。
I'm excited about all
the newspaper sales too.
我对一切都很兴奋
报纸销售也如此。
We haven't sold
any papers today.
我们还没卖
今天有什么论文。
What do you mean,
we haven't sold any newspapers?
你是什么意思，
我们还没有卖过报纸吗？
Certainly, this gentleman
would like a copy
of the Krabby Kronicle.
当然，这位先生
想要一份副本
克拉比纪事报。
Looks boring.
看起来很无聊。
Can I just have a Krabby Patty?
我可以只吃蟹黄饼吗？
Too boring?
太无聊了？
SpongeBob!
海绵宝宝！
What's the meaning of this?
这有什么意义呢？
Meaning of what, Mr. Krabs?
蟹老板，这是什么意思？
Local resident watches pole?
当地居民看杆？
No one's gonna pay
to read this malarkey.
没有人会付钱
读这个胡言乱语。
When you write these stories,
you got to use
a little imagination, boy.
当你写下这些故事时，
你必须使用
有点想象力，孩子。
Imagination.
想像力。
Yeah.
是的。
Maybe instead of
"man watches pole"
也许代替
“男人看杆子”
you could say something
like, oh, "man marries pole."
你可以说些什么
就像，哦，“男人嫁给了杆子。”
Then you could alter the photo
to fit the headline, and see?
然后你可以改变照片
适合标题，看到了吗？
Now, that's a juicy story.
现在，这是一个有趣的故事。
Mr. Krabs, isn't that lying?
蟹老板，这不是撒谎吗？
Don't think of it as lying, boy.
别以为这是撒谎，孩子。
Think of it as a practical joke.
将其视为一个恶作剧。
You know, something everybody
can have a good laugh about.
你知道，每个人都有一件事
可以好好笑一下。
The public expects a little
embellishment here and there
公众有点期待
到处点缀
so I want you to go out there
and get me a lead story
that'll sell.
所以我想让你出去
给我一个主要故事
那会卖的。
Mrs. Puff is gonna laugh
her hat off when she reads this.
泡芙太太要笑了
当她读到这篇文章时，她脱下了帽子。
Mr. Krabs: Boating teacher
in high speed chase!
Mr. Krabs：划船老师
高速追逐中！
I think you've finally
done it, boy!
我想你终于
做到了，孩子！
You've given me
a story that'll sell!
你给了我
一个会畅销的故事！
And sell it has.
并出售它。
yeah, but that isn't
the story I wrote.
是的，但那不是
我写的故事。
That's called
Editorial privilege, son.
这就是所谓的
编辑特权，儿子。
It gives it that extra "oomph"
to move units.
它赋予它额外的“魅力”
移动单位。
Besides, how could such
a little news story possibly
effect Mrs. Puff in any way?
再说了，怎么可能这样
可能是一个小新闻故事
对泡芙夫人有什么影响吗？
I can't believe such
a little news story
could have ruined my business.
我不敢相信这样
一个小新闻故事
可能会毁掉我的生意。
Let's see what there is to see.
让我们看看有什么可看的。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
Larry the lobster.
龙虾拉里。
Hm.
嗯。
I wonder what kind of dirt
he has under those muscles.
我想知道什么样的污垢
他有那些肌肉。
Ah-ha.
啊哈。
This looks shady.
这看起来很阴暗。
Very shady.
很阴暗。
Larry.
拉里.
Hey, tough guy.
嘿，硬汉。
Can I punch you in the gut?
我可以打你肚子吗？
Sure.
当然。
Everybody does.
每个人都这样做。
It won't hurt me a bit.
它不会伤害我一点点。
Told you it wouldn't hurt.
告诉过你这不会伤害。
Thanks, big guy.
谢谢大佬。
See you around.
再见。
Very interesting.
非常有趣。
Male voice: Out, out, out!
男声：出去，出去，出去！
Hey, what's the big idea?
嘿，有什么大主意吗？
This!
这！
Larry: Larry the loser
gets beaten up by pipsqueak?
拉里：失败者拉里
被pipsqueak殴打？
But... But... But...
但是……但是……但是……
No buts.
没有但是。
I can't have a wimp like you
destroying my gym's reputation.
我不能拥有像你这样的懦夫
毁了我健身房的声誉。
You're banned forever.
你被永远禁止了。
Hello, Larry.
你好，拉里。
Not now, SpongeBob.
现在不行，海绵宝宝。
Let me take in the fact
that my life is ruined.
让我接受事实
我的生活被毁了。
Ruined?
毁了？
What're you talking about?
你在说什么？
These lies someone
wrote about me.
这些谎言是某人
写了关于我的事。
Mr. Krabs: Thanks for
your business.
蟹老板：谢谢
你的事。
And here's your paper.
这是你的论文。
Mr. Krabs, can I have
a word with you?
蟹老板，我可以吃吗
跟你说句话吗？
Make it quick, boy.
快点吧，孩子。
These papers are selling faster
than we can print 'em.
这些报纸卖得更快
我们可以打印它们。
That's exactly what I wanted
to talk to you about, sir.
这正是我想要的
先生，要和你谈谈。
I don't think these stories
are doing anyone any good.
我不认为这些故事
对任何人都有好处。
Well, they're certainly
doing me some good.
嗯，他们当然是
对我有好处。
Can you believe it?
你能相信吗？
Look at all this loot!
看看这些战利品！
Yeah, but isn't there a way
we could write juicy stories
without hurting people?
是啊，但是没有办法吗
我们可以写出有趣的故事
不伤害人？
you just don't get it,
do you, boy?
你只是不明白，
你呢，男孩？
We're not hurting anyone.
我们没有伤害任何人。
We're just making their lives
interesting for everybody else.
我们只是在创造他们的生活
对其他人来说都很有趣。
Now, get out there
and fetch another story.
现在，出去吧
并获取另一个故事。
Oh, Karen.
哦，凯伦。
I think this is it.
我想就是这样了。
The chum stick that's finally
gonna drive Krabs
out of business.
最后的密棒
会开螃蟹
破产了。
Male voice: I think not.
男声：我想不是。
I'm Health Inspector Yellowtail.
我是卫生督察黄尾鱼。
I'm officially closing
down your restaurant.
我要正式关门了
下你的餐厅。
Why?
为什么？
I haven't done anything.
我什么也没做。
That's not what this says.
这不是这个意思。
Plankton: Plankton's chum
made of your chums?
浮游生物：浮游生物的密友
由你的好友组成？
The chum bucket
serves your friends
in more ways than one?
密友桶
为你的朋友服务
以多种方式？
What?
什么？
Who's to blame for this?
这该怪谁呢？
Who?
WHO？
世界卫生组织？
You're reaching new levels
of imagination, boy-o.
你正在达到新的水平
想象力，男孩-o。
Yeah, I know.
是的，我知道。
What's wrong, boy?
怎么了，男孩？
You sick or something?
你生病了还是怎么的？
Yes, Mr. Krabs.
是的，蟹老板。
You could say that.
你可以这么说。
Don't be silly, boy.
别傻了，孩子。
We're a success!
我们成功了！
Mr. Krabs, we're hurting people.
蟹老板，我们正在伤害人们。
Oh, baloney.
哦，胡说八道。
And you better start feelin'
right, 'cause if you don't
你最好开始感觉
是的，因为如果你不这样做
you can just kiss
your spatula goodbye.
你可以亲吻
你的抹刀再见。
Mr. Krabs, you wouldn't!
蟹老板，你不会的！
Oh, darn tootin', I would.
哦，该死的，我会的。
Now get out there
and bring me a juicy one.
现在出去吧
给我带来一份多汁的。
Aye-aye, Captain.
是的，船长。
Sorry, "fellers".
对不起，“家伙们”。
This is a private tree dome.
这是一个私人树顶。
I had no idea it talked.
我不知道它会说话。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
We're from the Neptunian
Science Committee
我们来自海王星
科学委员会
and we've come to confiscate
all your science awards.
我们是来没收的
你所有的科学奖项。
Haven't you read
today's headlines?
你没读过吗
今天的头条新闻？
It can't even read.
它甚至无法读取。
Why are you...
你为什么...
Oh, give me that!
哦，给我那个！
Sandy Cheeks or Sandy Chump?
桑迪脸颊还是桑迪笨蛋？
Bushy-tailed brainiac really
a slow-witted squirrel?
浓尾智者真的
一只迟钝的松鼠？
By SpongeBob SquarePants?
海绵宝宝？
That yellow sidewinder thinks
he can do that to me?
那黄响尾蛇认为
他可以这样对我吗？
Oh, boy.
哦，男孩。
We'd better scram.
我们最好赶紧滚吧。
The dumb ones are always
the most violent.
笨蛋总是
最暴力的。
You've really outdone
yourself this time.
你真的已经不甘示弱了
这次你自己。
Mr. Krabs, I can't write
these stories anymore.
蟹老板，我不会写
这些故事不再了。
Come on,
that's a bunch of hooey.
来吧，
那是一堆胡言乱语。
I've seen people's lives
ruined with my own eyes.
我见过人们的生活
被我亲眼所毁。
People want wild, juicy stories.
人们想要狂野、有趣的故事。
That's what sells.
这就是卖的东西。
Now, I want your little,
yellow noggin to come up
with the wildest story ever.
现在，我想要你的小，
黄头出现
有史以来最疯狂的故事。
One that'll top all the others.
一款将超越所有其他产品的产品。
Well, gee, Mr. Krabs,
I've written about
everyone in town.
好吧，哎呀，蟹老板先生，
我写过关于
镇上的每个人。
Any ideas, sir?
有什么想法吗，先生？
Surprise me.
让我惊讶。
Give me a shocker.
给我一个震撼。
Good night, boy.
晚安，孩子。
I'll check on you
tomorrow morning.
我会检查你的情况
明天早上。
And remember,
the wildest story ever.
请记住，
有史以来最疯狂的故事。
Ah, the wildest story ever, huh?
啊，有史以来最疯狂的故事，是吧？
How's it goin', lad?
怎么样，小伙子？
Ah, it's a surprise.
啊，真是意外啊。
Mr. Krabs: Excellent.
蟹老板：太棒了。
We're gonna sell out in no time.
我们很快就会卖完。
We'll have to do
another printing.
我们必须做
另一种印刷。
huh?
嗯？
Taskmaster!
监工！
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
You should know!
你应该知道！
Krabs overworks employees?
蟹老板让员工过度劳累？
Reaps reward?
收获回报？
Krabby Kronicle mastermind
behind bogus stories
Krabby Kronicle 策划者
虚假故事背后
pays his tired,
underage reporter pennies
while he rakes in the dough?
付出他的疲惫，
未成年记者便士
当他耙面团的时候？
How could you do that
to such an innocent child?
你怎么能这么做
对这样一个无辜的孩子？
It's sick and inhumane.
这是病态且不人道的。
Not to mention the fact
that he's written lies about us.
更不用说事实
他写了关于我们的谎言。
I lost my restaurant
because of you.
我失去了我的餐厅
因为你。
And I thought  I  was evil.
我以为我是邪恶的。
All the kids in town want
to beat me up for lunch money.
镇上所有的孩子都想要
为了午饭钱而打我。
And I've had to go back
to watching daytime television.
我不得不回去
看白天的电视。
That's it!
就是这样！
We're taking our money back!
我们要拿回我们的钱！
Mr. Krabs, are you ok?
蟹老板，你还好吗？
How can I be ok
when me money's gone?
我怎样才能好
当我的钱没了？
All gone.
全部消失了。
it just goes to show,
trying to make an easy buck
doesn't pay.
它只是表明，
试图轻松赚钱
不付钱。
Or does it?
或者确实如此？
Get me some scissors, boy-o.
给我一些剪刀，男孩。
It's time to use  my  imagination.
是时候发挥我的想象力了。
Patrick: Hey, guys?
帕特里克：嘿，伙计们？
Can you fix me and the wife up
a couple of Krabby Patties?
你能帮我和妻子安顿一下吗
几个蟹黄饼？